<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Curiositas</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Curiositas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:41:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writeups of some FCSC challenges</title>
      <link>/posts/fcsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 21:47:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fcsc/</guid>
      <description>This are little write-ups for challenges of the France Cybersecurity Challenge CTF of 2020. I finished 123/633 in the Senior category and 217/1591 in the general ranking. I will try harder next year, I promise.
Summary:
 Intro Le rat conteur Poney TarteTatin Babel Web Misc Randomito Baby Xoring Networks Reverse Infiltrate Web Rainbow Pages EnterTheDungeon Revision Bestiary   Intro Le rat conteur openssl enc -aes-128-ctr -d -in flag.jpg.enc -out flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAMUCTF 2020: Obituary 1 &amp; 2</title>
      <link>/posts/obituary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 10:27:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/obituary/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Obituary 395&amp;#43;398 points Hey, shoot me over your latest version of the code. I have a simple nc session up, just pass it over when you&amp;rsquo;re ready.
You&amp;rsquo;re using vim, right? You should use it; it&amp;rsquo;ll change your life. I basically depend on it for everything these days!
   Obituary 1 We are given an OpenVPN configuration file. This will allow us to connect to the VPN and have access to 172.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>infernoCTF: Weakened Keys</title>
      <link>/posts/weakened_keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 11:15:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weakened_keys/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Weakened Keys 400 points Local politicians and their anti crypto opinions have forced us to dumb down our AES encryption. It&amp;rsquo;s OK because we think we can still use these weakened keys and still encrypt our message securely by encrypting it twice. Have a look at our code and see what you think.
sample_encrypted_base64 = &#39;0mu0T97looX5/Oorw8ASGxfqMqrNoFajZupXrjtIAj7ECJdQXZzEmbEwdRV2J2MI&#39;
sample_plaintext = &#39;Double AES encryption for twice the strength.Win&#39;
flag_encrypted_base64 = &#39;lIZMVkA+pbiOxh3nNdV2bWz3gXovIy4fG7yCHa5FT44=&#39;
Hint: our keys only include printable ASCII characters</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:41:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World My name is Louis and I&amp;rsquo;m an engineering student interested in cybersecurity.
This blog has been made with Hugo with the theme hugo-classic, customized to my needs.
Tools I use I use the one and only text editor, Vim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santhacklaus 2019: Jacques! Au secours!</title>
      <link>/posts/jacques_au_secours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:31:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/jacques_au_secours/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Jacques! Au secours! 400 points One of our VIP clients, who wishes to remain anonymous, has apparently been hacked and all their important documents are now corrupted.
Can you help us recover the files? We found a strange piece of software that might have caused all of this.
File: chall_files.zip
  The challenge gives us a zip file with:
 a &amp;lsquo;vacation pictures&amp;rsquo; folder containing  4 encrypted images  DCIM-0533.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>