<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto on Curiositas</title>
    <link>/categories/crypto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crypto on Curiositas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 21:47:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writeups of some FCSC challenges</title>
      <link>/posts/fcsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 21:47:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fcsc/</guid>
      <description>This are little write-ups for challenges of the France Cybersecurity Challenge CTF of 2020. I finished 123/633 in the Senior category and 217/1591 in the general ranking. I will try harder next year, I promise.
Summary  Intro  Le rat conteur Poney TarteTatin Babel Web   Misc  Randomito Baby Xoring Networks   Reverse  Infiltrate   Web  Rainbow Pages EnterTheDungeon Revision Bestiary     Intro Le rat conteur openssl enc -aes-128-ctr -d -in flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>infernoCTF: Weakened Keys</title>
      <link>/posts/weakened_keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 11:15:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weakened_keys/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Weakened Keys 400 points Local politicians and their anti crypto opinions have forced us to dumb down our AES encryption. It&amp;rsquo;s OK because we think we can still use these weakened keys and still encrypt our message securely by encrypting it twice. Have a look at our code and see what you think.
sample_encrypted_base64 = &#39;0mu0T97looX5/Oorw8ASGxfqMqrNoFajZupXrjtIAj7ECJdQXZzEmbEwdRV2J2MI&#39;
sample_plaintext = &#39;Double AES encryption for twice the strength.Win&#39;
flag_encrypted_base64 = &#39;lIZMVkA+pbiOxh3nNdV2bWz3gXovIy4fG7yCHa5FT44=&#39;
Hint: our keys only include printable ASCII characters</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santhacklaus 2019: Jacques! Au secours!</title>
      <link>/posts/jacques_au_secours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:31:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/jacques_au_secours/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Jacques! Au secours! 400 points One of our VIP clients, who wishes to remain anonymous, has apparently been hacked and all their important documents are now corrupted.
Can you help us recover the files? We found a strange piece of software that might have caused all of this.
File: chall_files.zip
  The challenge gives us a zip file with:
 a &amp;lsquo;vacation pictures&amp;rsquo; folder containing  4 encrypted images  DCIM-0533.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>